(
"ai_sub_version": "1.11.0",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 3,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
ビターチョコデコレーション
作詞・作曲：syudou
Bitter Choco Decoration
Lyrics & Composition: syudou
人を過度に信じないように
Don't trust people too much
愛さないように
Don't love them
期待しないように
Don't expect anything
孤毒な角が立たないように
So you don't stick out in your solitude
気取らぬように
Don't put on airs
目立たぬように
Don't stand out
誰一人傷つけぬように
So you don't hurt anyone
虐めぬように
Don't bully anyone
殺さぬように
Don't kill anyone
隠し持った牙がバレないように
So the fangs you've hidden aren't found out
威張らぬように
Don't be arrogant
軽いジョークや
Light jokes and
リップサービスも忘れないように
don't forget the lip service either
どんな時も笑って愛嬌振りまくように
Laugh and flash your charm no matter what
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration
とにかく言われた通り召し上がれ
Anyway, eat it up just as you're told
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration
食わず嫌いはちゃんと直さなきゃ
You have to fix that picky eating
頭空っぽその後に
After your head's empty
残る心が本物なら
if the heart that remains is real
きっと君だって同じ事
surely you'll do the same
さあ、今すぐ跪け
Now, kneel down this instant
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter Choco Decoration
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
無駄に知恵が回らされるように
So that useless wisdom is spun around.
離されるように　解るように
So that I'm separated, so that I understand.
ガム噛んで口を閉ざすように
Chewing gum to keep my mouth shut.
笑わすより笑われるように
Better to be laughed at than to make others laugh.
人をちゃんと敬うように
So that I respect people properly.
崇めるように　称えるように
So that I worship, so that I praise.
有象無象にならないように
So that I don't become part of the masses.
ふざけないように
So that I don't mess around.
集団参賀の終止系
The final form of collective worship.
またへいこらへいこら言っちゃって
Bowing and scraping again.
「あれ前髪超絶最高じゃん」とか
"Oh, your bangs look absolutely amazing."
どうでもいいのに言っちゃって
Saying things that don't matter.
毎度毎度も限界執着的
Every single time, borderline obsessive.
社会のシューターです
A shooter for society.
決して発狂しないように
So that I never go insane.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
時に孤独な愛は君を汚す
Sometimes, lonely love stains you.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
鳥肌のあと一口さのあと
After the goosebumps, after a single bite.
初めはあんな大層な
At first, it was such a grand...
大言壮語を並べたが
...collection of big words.
嫌や嫌やも好きなうち
Even saying no is a sign of interest.
いやはやしかし今日が初めてで
Well, well, but today is the first time...
こんなとは出来見センスあるよ
...you've got some talent to do this much.
恋する季節に
In the season of love.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
恋する気持ちで
With feelings of love.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
F.U.C.K.Y.O.U.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
皆が望む理想に憧れて
Longing for the ideal everyone wants.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
個性や情を全部焼き払い
Burning away all individuality and emotion.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
欲やエゴは殺して土に埋め
Kill desire and ego, bury them in the dirt.
ビターチョコデコレーション
Bitter choco decoration.
僕は大人にやっと成ったよママ
I've finally become an adult, Mama.
明日の規則の端を
The edge of tomorrow's rules.
地獄は続くどこまでも
Hell continues everywhere.
あだこうだ言わず今だけを
Don't complain, just focus on the now.
こどものころの気持ちのままで
Keep your childhood feelings.
意地張らずにやってこうぜ
Let's do this without being stubborn.
ああ思い出したあの時の生真面目さな
Ah, I remembered that seriousness from back then.
やっぱいいや
Actually, never mind.
サイコロ...
The dice...
5が出た
I got a 5.
何これ？
What's this?
椅子？
A chair?
One, two, one...
Deal with the devil
アブダワヨのツネ
It's the way of the world.
クズ引いた後動じない
Don't flinch after drawing a dud.
肝心なの正体
The important thing is your true identity.
出し抜いてサバイブ
Outwit them and survive.
行き着く先には
At the end of the road...
HEAVEN OR HELL?
この世界のルール
The rules of this world...
たった一つ　勝者が正義
...only one thing: the winner is justice.
女は度胸
A woman's courage.
散らしてセンスを　アイツは
Spreading her sense, that guy is...
やれることなんだってやる　アタシは
I'll do whatever it takes, I am...
賭ケグルイのQueen
...the Kakegurui Queen.
お願い　悦頂戴
Please, give me pleasure.
震えてるわよ　札束
The stacks of cash are shaking.
見分けもつかないわ　私をモノにする
I can't even tell them apart; you'll make me yours.
あなたの髪の1本まで全部
Every single strand of your hair.
100万倍　愛絶頂で　酔わせるわよ
A million times more, at the peak of love, I'll make you drunk.
坊や　お残しはさせないわ
Little boy, I won't let you leave anything behind.
見分けもつかない　合格不合格
I can't tell the difference, pass or fail.
たまらないわ　スリル誰にも触らせない
I can't stand it, the thrill, I won't let anyone touch it.
このマネー　100万倍　愛絶頂でさあ
This money, a million times more, at the peak of love, come on.
覚悟決めて　トドメ刺される前のMy Heart
Make up your mind, my heart before the final blow.
欲しいの？悦じゃねー
Do you want it? It's not pleasure.
まだベビー
Still a baby.
全然負けないわ
I won't lose at all.
感じさせてよ愛を
Let me feel your love.
あなた正体は
Your true identity is...
ほら逃がさない
Look, I won't let you escape.
見せてあげる 秘密って甘い毒
I'll show you, secrets are sweet poison
仕掛けて 罠にハメるわ
Setting a trap to catch you
誘惑誘う 蛇のよう
Luring you in like a snake
思考を止めて パラダイスへ
Stop thinking and head for paradise
何も知らない ような顔で 躍るわ あなたを
With an innocent face, I'll dance you around
かすれし その指先
Those trembling fingertips
読みきって 劣勢だわ
I see through them, you're at a disadvantage
賭けりゃいいんでしょ？ 全部 読み切ってるわ
Should I just bet? I've read everything
デッドだって ヘンに隠さない
I won't strangely hide even if it's dead
どんな小さなズレも 研ぎ澄ませ
Hone every tiny deviation
見逃さないわ
I won't miss a thing
アンデッドな愛でしょ？ カモ相手はゴメンだわ
It's undead love, right? I'm not interested in easy targets
修正してあげる
I'll fix it for you
狙った獲物は逃さない
I won't let my targeted prey escape
唇濡らして いただきます オマエを
Wetting my lips, I'll devour you
ダイヤのジャックで 手が揃うわ
A Jack of Diamonds completes the hand
微笑みは 殺め始末だけ
Smiles only for finishing off
熱いポーカーフェイスはパーフェクト
The intense poker face is perfect
一部のスキも見せたりしないわ
I won't show even a sliver of vulnerability
執念感じて 震えるわ
Feeling the obsession and trembling
お遊びは おしまいよ
The playing is over
見てばかりいないで
Don't just watch
欲しがらせて
Make me want you
あたしが欲しくて たまらない
I want it so bad I can't stand it
負けるのは怖い？ 跪け
Afraid of losing? Kneel down
読みきって 劣勢だわ
I see through it all, you're at a disadvantage
あたしのものにする
I'll make you mine
あなたの髪の 1本まで 全部
Every single strand of your hair, everything
アンデッドな 愛でしょ？
It's undead love, right?
覚悟決めて
Make up your mind
灰になるまで 打ってあげる
I'll strike until it turns to ash
欲しがるでしょ？ まだベイベー
You want it, don't you? Still, baby
誰にも 負けない
I won't lose to anyone
感じさせてあげる
I'll make you feel it
あー...。
Ah...
あれ？ 椅子 無くなっちゃった。
Huh? The chair's gone.
あー、もう少し座らせてほしかったー。
Ah, I wanted to sit for a bit longer.
はい、みんなー！ 見えてる？ 聞こえてるー？
Okay, everyone! Can you see me? Can you hear me?
ホロライブ所属の癒やし系ハーフエルフ、アキロゼことアキ・ローゼンタールです！
I'm the healing half-elf from Hololive, Aki Rosenthal, also known as AkiRose!
ハロハロハロ、アロナー！
Halo-halo-halo, Alona!
えー、今回のアキロゼ生誕祭2026へようこそー！
Um, welcome to this AkiRose Birthday Festival 2026!
早速ね、なんか色々行われていたんですが、
A lot was happening right from the start, but...
一体今回のライブはどうなっちゃうのか、
I wonder what's going to happen in this show.
ぜひ最後まで一瞬もお見逃しなくお願いします。
So please don't miss a single moment until the end.
今回のライブのハッシュタグは「#アキロゼ生誕祭2026」、
The hashtag for this show is "#AkiRoseBirthdayFestival2026."
こちらをつけて、Xにたくさんポストしてね！
Please use it to post a lot on X!
もちろん、可愛いスクショや、綺麗なスクショもたくさん撮って、合わせて投稿してください。
Of course, take lots of cute and beautiful screenshots and post them too.
ライブが終わった後、アキロゼ見に行きます！ 見てねー！
I'll go check them after the live! Look forward to it!
あ、チャンネル登録もよろしくね！ オッケー？
Oh, and please subscribe to the channel! Okay?
ポチッとして？ はい、ありがとう。
Click it? Yes, thank you.
おっ？ お, おっ？ 何だ何だ？
Oh? Oh, oh? What's this?
んー。 ていうか、ここどこなんだろう？
Hmm... I mean, where am I?
お！ あんなところにルーレットがある！
Oh! There's a roulette wheel over there!
え、回るのかな？
Eh, I wonder if it spins?
おっ！ 回った！ えー、すごい！
Oh! It spun! Wow, amazing!
おー、回った。
Oh, it's spinning.
えー、何が出るかな？
Eh, I wonder what'll come up?
次は何だろう
What's next?
あ、え、お、え？
Ah, eh, oh, eh?
なに？なに？
What? What?
どうなっちゃうの？
What's going to happen?
え？あ、えー？
Eh? Ah, ehh?
ピース？
Peace?
お、んー、なんだ？
Oh, hmm, what is it?
A-Happy!
あらめば人の子
If I appear as a human child
A-Lucky!
とならざるものも
Even those who are not
お愛嬌、目指せよ
Show some charm, aim for it
いっそ生きてる証ね
It's surely proof of being alive
目を逸らした格好も
Even with eyes averted
退屈な未来も
Even a boring future
閑散に、ヤレヤレ
Quietly, oh dear
古今東西ピースピース
Everywhere and anytime, peace peace
UNDEAD
作詞・作曲：Ayase
Lyrics & Composition: Ayase
A-Happy!
A-Lucky!
Be Happy!
UNDEAD
ねえねえねえなんだかどうして
Hey hey hey, somehow why
戦ってるようなそんな気がするの
Do I feel like I'm fighting?
逃げられない、痛くもない
Can't escape, doesn't even hurt
ここの自分
The me right here
トドメ刺し死んでる
Delivering the final blow, dead
止められない対決
An unstoppable confrontation
痛い消えて言いたい
It hurts, disappear, I want to say
記憶の奥底
Deep in the memories
残念もういないのに
Too bad, even though I'm no longer there
あれ？そっちがアイロニーね
Eh? That's the irony
透かされてるのは今の自分
The one being seen through is my current self
ナンセンス、消えないレッテル
Nonsense, an indelible label
否、弱コンプレックス
No, a weak complex
取り憑かれてるみたい
It's like I'm possessed
巻き付いたまままだ離れない
Coiled around, still not letting go
在りし日の自分
My former self
UNDEAD
信じたいお前とお前の連鎖
I want to believe in the chain of you and you
生きてるかと問われ続ける答えさ
The answer to the constant question: "Are you alive?"
不条理に甘んじて満足するなよ
Don't be satisfied with submitting to absurdity
幸せになろうとしないなんて業だ
Not trying to be happy is karma
この世、この世は奇々怪々ファンタジー
This world, this world is a bizarre fantasy
次は鬼が出るか蛇が出るか
Will an ogre or a snake come next?
果て果てやっと始まる物語
At last, the story finally begins
覚悟を決めな化け物の子
Prepare yourself, child of a monster
古今東西ピースピース
Everywhere and anytime, peace peace
Ah, the future can change the past
Past, future, love the future
ねえなんだかどうして未来になんぞなの
Hey, somehow why is it toward the future?
否もまだ、曖昧なの、予報がして
Even now, it's still vague, forecasting
もう十分生きてる意識だってプレイで
The consciousness of already living enough is just play
食傷、素敵なんて聞き事の気配もない
Boredom, not even a sign of anything wonderful to hear
残念、積んだ経験、因果形骸化した
Too bad, accumulated experience, cause and effect have decayed
死はド退屈の進化
Death is the evolution of extreme boredom
要は刺激が欲しいんだ
The point is, I want stimulation
飽きちゃった、成れの果て
I'm tired of it, the end result
ナンセンス、飾ってくガイダンス
Nonsense, decorating guidance
セルフコンプライアンス
Self-compliance
使い果たしてくみたい
It's like I'm using it all up
巻き付いたまままだ
Still wound around
あれもこれもそれも
That, this, that too
同じ味がする
They all taste the same
UNDEAD
信じたいお前とお前の連鎖
I want to believe in the chain of you and you
いつのような過去も未来も今にあるんだ
Past and future alike are in the now
生きてることを愚直に果たせよ
Honestly fulfill the act of living
目指せハッピーエンド
Aim for a happy ending
信じたいお前に今言ってるんだ
I want to believe, I'm telling you now
幸せを諦めてしまうな一人であるな
Don't give up on happiness, don't be alone
ただ苦しみに慣れて絶えているだけじゃ
If you're just getting used to pain and enduring
死んでるも同然、屍のUNDEAD
You're as good as dead, a corpse of an UNDEAD
あらめば人の子とならざるものも
If I appear as a human child, and even those who aren't
さあ今目指せよ生きてるんだろう？
Now aim for it, aren't you alive?
不器用に誰も幸せになれるだろ
Clumsily, anyone can become happy, right?
もう全部全部お前だ
It's all, all you
古今東西ピースピース
Everywhere and anytime, peace peace
死んでもなおピースピース
Even if dead, peace peace
Ah, the future can change the past
Past, future, love the future
人となれど心いつでも最高と
Become human, heart always at its best
この化け物ばかり、物語
A story of only these monsters
ハッピーエンド、ピースピース！
Happy ending, peace peace!
愛♡スクリーム！
作詞：aim
作曲：DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
Ai Scream!
Lyrics: aim
Composition: DJ Chika a.k.a. INHERIT / Hayato Yamamoto
愛♡スクリーム！
Ai Scream!
教えてもっと あなたのこと
Tell me more about you
聞かせてもっと あなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice
こんなドキドキ
This pounding heart
もう隠せない
Can't hide it anymore
Oh I need you, Oh I want you
友達は卒業
Graduating from being friends
運命の証
Proof of destiny
見つけてほしいな
I want you to find me
勇気を出して
Summon your courage
Woo!
見つめる作戦
Operation: Staring
Hey!
無邪気な一杯
An innocent scoop
For you! Oh...
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this crush, with this love
メロメロに溶けちゃうよ
I'm melting head over heels
(ちゃうよ)
(Melting)
Yeah yeah yeah
気づいて My darling
Notice me, my darling
とろける 大好き
I love you so much I'm melting
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
Okay!
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
はあとちゃん！
Haato-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
チョコミントよりあなた！
More than choc-mint, I like you!
るるちゃん！
Ruby-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
ストロベリーフレーバーよりあなた！
More than strawberry flavor, I like you!
アキちゃん！
Aki-chan!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
クッキー&クリームよりあなた！
More than cookies & cream, I like you!
みんな！
Everyone!
はい！
Yes!
何が好き？
What do you like?
もちろん大好き！アイスクリーム！
Of course we love it! Ice cream!
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this crush, with this love
メロメロに溶けちゃうよ
I'm melting head over heels
Yeah yeah yeah
気づいて My darling
Notice me, my darling
とろける 大好き
I love you so much I'm melting
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
Okay!
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
お願い見つけて My darling
Please find me, my darling
お願い気づいて My darling
Please notice me, my darling
Wow! 勇気を出して
Wow! Summon your courage
近づく作戦
Operation: Getting closer
Hey! 緊張が触れて
Hey! Our nervousness touches
For you! Oh...
止められない
Can't be stopped
Yeah yeah yeah
この恋 この愛で
With this crush, with this love
メロメロに溶けちゃうよ
I'm melting head over heels
Yeah yeah yeah
気づいて My darling
Notice me, my darling
それはあなた
It's you
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
Okay!
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
Okay!
アイ・アイ・スクリーム
I, I scream
スクリーム
Scream
叫びましょう
Let's shout it out
アイスクリーム！
Ice cream!
おーっ、元気もらえて、面白くって、オレンジで
Oh, it's energizing, it's fun, it's orange...
シャンパンコール得意な人いないかなー？
Is there anyone good at champagne calls?
それ俺やないかーい！
That would be me!
イケナイ太陽
Forbidden Sun
ちょっとでいいから見せてくれないか
Won't you show me, even just a little?
お前のセクシー・フェロモンで俺メロメロ
Your sexy pheromones have me head over heels
冷めちゃいそうでもいけないの
Even if it seems like I'll cool down, it's naughty
喉元高鳴る鼓動 止められないわ
The thumping in my throat, I can't stop it
Ah 交わす言葉の記憶解く
Ah, unraveling the memories of our exchanged words
瞳もトロ、動きに揺れ動く
Even my eyes are melting, swaying with your movements
濡れた髪を撫でた そしてAh
I stroked your wet hair, and then... Ah
ABC 続かない
ABC, it's not going on
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's not good enough, is it?
だってココロの奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
オレの青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth is more than just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out deep inside
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
It definitely has to be you
オレはイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
Ah 赤い糸なんておとぎ話
Ah, the red thread of fate is just a fairy tale
でもしたごころでさえ信じたいの
But I want to believe even in ulterior motives
オレは正しい キミも正しい
I'm right, and you're right too
とにかくもう左右されないぜ
Anyway, I won't be swayed anymore
騙し騙され胸うずく
Deceiving and being deceived, my heart aches
芝居だより盛り上げるよ
I'll liven things up with a performance
吐息が耳に触れた二人 Ah
Our breaths touched each other's ears, Ah
ABC 続かない
ABC, it's not going on
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's not good enough, is it?
だってココロの奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
私の青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth is more than just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out deep inside
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
It definitely has to be you
私イケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
交わす言葉の記憶遠く 口元の動きに揺れ動く
The memories of words shared are distant, swaying to the movement of our lips
濡れた髪を撫でた そしてAh
I stroked your wet hair, and then... Ah
ABC... ABC 続かない
ABC... ABC, it's not going on
そんなんじゃダメじゃない
That's not good enough, is it?
だってココロの奥は違うんじゃない
Because deep in your heart, it's different, isn't it?
オレの青春そんなもんじゃない
My youth is more than just that
熱く奥で果てたいよ
I want to burn out deep inside
きっとキミじゃなきゃヤダよ
It definitely has to be you
オレはイケナイ太陽
I'm the naughty sun
絡み合う糸はキミと
The threads intertwining are with you
オレをむすぶ赤い糸
The red thread that binds me
はぁ〜、はぁ〜。みんな、来てくれてありがとう！
*panting* Thank you all for coming!
ということで、お友達が来てくれたので、せっかくなので自己紹介してもらおうと思います！
So, since my friends are here, I'd like to have them introduce themselves!
まずはプルルちゃんから！
First, Pururu-chan!
はーい！
Hi!
天使と悪魔のプルプルエンジェルデビル、甘噛プルルです！
I'm the angel and demon Purupuru Angel-Devil, Amagami Pururu!
アキロゼ〜、お誕生日おめでとう！
Akirose, happy birthday!
ありがとう！いや〜とっても楽しかったですね！
Thank you! Man, that was really fun!
最高！そして続いてカルビちゃーん！
Awesome! Next, Karubi-chan!
はい！お肉の国のお姫様、赤見カルビです！
Hi! I'm the princess of the Kingdom of Meat, Akami Karubi!
アキロゼ、誕生日おめでとう！
Akirose, happy birthday!
いいライブって、友達とのライブ初めてだからさ、マジで嬉しかったよ。本当に呼んでくれて、またやろうぜ！
This is a great live show. It's my first time performing with friends, so I'm really happy. Thanks for inviting me. Let's do it again!
またやろう！素晴らしい！そして最後に、ずずさん！
Let's! Wonderful! And finally, Zuzu-san!
はーい！僕のこと知らない人いると思うんで自己紹介だけさせてください！
Hi! I think some people might not know me, so let me just introduce myself!
雨降ってザーザー 症状事態はG.G. オレの名前は Z.Z.Z.Z. ずずでございます！
Rain falling za-za, my condition is G.G., my name is Z-Z-Z-Z Zuzu!
いや、お誕生日おめでとう！
Anyway, happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
はいおはよー！
Good morning!
おい忙しい人気者だ、お忙しい人気者だ。
Look at this busy popular person.
アキちゃんおめでとー！
Congrats, Aki-chan!
お誕生日おめでとう！ハッピーバースデー！ハッピーバースデー！
Happy birthday! Happy birthday! Happy birthday!
ありがとー！めちゃめちゃ、ありがとー！
Thank you! Thank you so very much!
あー、賑やかで楽しかったー。
Ah, that was so lively and fun.
JANE DOE
作詞・作曲：米津玄師
Lyrics/Composition: Kenshi Yonezu
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world
二人だけみたいだね
there's only the two of us, right?
なんて少しだけ
I just ended up
夢を見てしまっただけ
dreaming like that for a little bit.
爪先に月明かり
Moonlight on my toes
花束の香り
the scent of a bouquet
弓に触れる指
fingers touching the bow.
さよなら
Goodbye
もう行かなきゃ
I have to go now
何もかも忘れて
forgetting about everything.
ガラスの上を　裸足のまま歩く
Walking on glass, barefoot.
痛むごとに　血が流れて落ちていく
With every step that hurts, blood flows and drips.
お願い　その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints
会い来て
and come see me.
錆びたプールに　放たれていく金魚
Goldfish being released into a rusted pool.
葛籠の中に　隠した林檎
An apple hidden inside a wicker trunk.
萎びた君の肌に　残る傷跡
The scars remaining on your withered skin.
犬のように　泳いだ迷子
A lost child who swam like a dog.
どこにいるの？ / どこにいるよ？
Where are you? / I was right there.
何を言ってるの？ / 何を見てるよ？
What are you saying? / What are you looking at?
この世を間違いで見渡そう
Let's look out over this world with mistakes.
そばにいたよ　遊びに行こうよ
I was by your side, let's go out and play.
どこにいるの？
Where are you?
ガラスの上を　裸足のまま歩く
Walking on glass, barefoot.
痛むごとに　血が流れて落ちていく
With every step that hurts, blood flows and drips.
お願い　その赤い足跡を辿って
Please, follow those red footprints
会い来て
and come see me.
まるでこの世界で
It's as if in this world
二人だけみたいだね
there's only the two of us, right?
なんて少しだけ
I just ended up
夢を見てしまっただけ
dreaming like that for a little bit.
さあ、選択の時だ。
Now, it's time to choose.
コイン。
Coin.
はっ
Hah.
このコインは…
This coin is...
なあ、そうか。
Ah, I see.
君はそっちなんだね。
So you're on that side.
そっち？
That side?
ここに座って。
Sit here.
えっ。
Eh.
この後は、君次第だよ。
After this, it's up to you.
Whisper Whisper Whisper
作詞・作曲：Azari
Lyrics/Music: Azari
忘れられないのは この目のせい
I can't forget it, because of these eyes
赤く残る過ち 甘噛みの跡
The red mistakes remain, like love bites
溢れ出した愛は 止めどない
The overflowing love won't stop
誰もいない間に 悪魔を捜す
I search for the devil while nobody's looking
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から 呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch me yet
この檻を抜け出して 悪魔は駆ける
Escaping this cage, the devil runs
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ 噛み殺す夜
A night where I bite back the words I want to say
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って 悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God, I spend my time with the devil
あいまいみー 夢見てたい あなたに
I-My-Me, I want to keep dreaming for you
そっと気付かせて あげたいだけ
I just want to make you quietly realize
おお あなたにも
Oh, for you too
消えまい 傷を隠したい あなたに
I won't fade away, I want to hide my wounds from you
そっと悩ませて あげたいだけ
I just want to make you quietly worry
おお あなたにも
Oh, for you too
おお 悪魔を捜す
Oh, searching for the devil
作り笑いはこの耳のせい
The fake smile is because of these ears
深い壁の中から 呼びかける声
A voice calling out from within the deep walls
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ触らせない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't let you touch me yet
この檻を抜け出して 悪魔は駆ける
Escaping this cage, the devil runs
鏡の前でこの口のせい
In front of the mirror, because of this mouth
伝えたい言葉さえ 噛み殺す夜
A night where I bite back the words I want to say
Whisper Whisper Whisper まだ打ち明けない
Whisper Whisper Whisper, I won't reveal it yet
神様を裏切って 悪魔と過ごす
Betraying God, I spend my time with the devil
BANG!!!
作詞：ryo (supercell) / 作曲：Giga
Lyrics: ryo (supercell) / Music: Giga
好き 嫌い 常識 I don't care! 吹っ飛ばせ BANG!!!
Like, dislike, common sense, I don't care! Blow it all away, BANG!!!
多数決 マジョリティ あたしに負けはなし
Majority vote, majority, no defeat for me
ここまでって引かれた そのボーダー誰のルール？
The border drawn "this far," whose rule is that?
あの日乗り越えたウィークポイント
The weak point I overcame that day
強くなったあたしが 笑い飛ばしてあげる
I've grown stronger, I'll laugh it off for you
言いたいことは言う
I'll say what I want to say
やりたくないことはしない
I won't do what I don't want to do
悪意気にしない
I don't care about malice
みんな違うの当然だし
It's natural for everyone to be different
あたしも変わらない 目の前の自分
I won't change either, the person right here in front of me
Everybody say, "I want to be free!"
本音も何も言わないんじゃ それじゃ何も変えられない
If you don't speak your mind, nothing will ever change
Everybody say, "I want to be more!"
我儘な自分 肯定
Affirming my selfish self
生きてるんだ あたし
I am living my life
ねぇ 生きてるんだ あたし
Hey, I am living my life
Wow wow wow 生きてるんだ あたし
Wow wow wow, I am living my life
今宵 生まれたその時から 選んできたんだ
I've been choosing since the moment I was born tonight
思い出せ あたしはあたしだ
Remember, I am who I am
不確かなことなんて 何ひとつない 嘘じゃない
There's nothing uncertain, and that's no lie
生きたい自分に
Into the person I want to be
好き 嫌い 常識 I don't care! 吹っ飛ばせ BANG!!!
Like, dislike, common sense, I don't care! Blow it all away, BANG!!!
狂ってんならさ 手にこのリリック勝負
If you're crazy, let's settle it with these lyrics
わからす 挑発 下向いた 舌打ちからの咆哮
I'll make you understand, a provocation, a click of the tongue, then a roar
Excuse me!
...返しくらえ
...Take that in return!
パンチライン　聴かせてあげる　Ah
I'll let you hear the punchline, Ah
やってから考えな Now
Think about it after you do it, Now
私がついてるから Ah
Because I'm with you, Ah
Everybody say I want to be free
喰らえこのビート　空中感
Take this beat, the feeling of floating
全部黙らす Show!
A show that silences everything!
目覚ませ起きてよ
Wake up, get up
Wake up, Wake up　いっそまた
Wake up, Wake up, let's just...
ねぇ　いっそまた
Hey, let's just...
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
I've been choosing it since the moment I was born
思い出せ　私は私だ
Remember, I am who I am
不可能なことなど　何ひとつもない　嘘じゃないぞ
There is nothing impossible, and that's no lie
生まれたその時から選んできたんだ
You've been choosing it since the moment you were born
思い出せ　あなたはあなただ
Remember, you are who you are
不可能なことなど　何ひとつもない　嘘じゃないなりたい自分に
There is nothing impossible, and that's no lie, to the person you want to be
Against, Keep, Try, To see, I don't care, Foot of the path
Bad Apple!!
作詞：Haruka 作曲：ZUN
Lyrics: Haruka Composition: ZUN
流れてく時の中ででも　気だるさが
Even in the midst of flowing time, listlessness...
ほらグルグル回って　私から離れる
See, it spins around and moves away from me
心も見えないわ　そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I don't know it
自分から動くこともなく　時の隙間に
Without moving of my own accord, into the gaps of time...
流され続けて知らないわ　周りのことなど
Being washed away continuously, I don't know anything about my surroundings
私は私それだけ
I am me, and that's all
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
It's useless to speak my own words
悲しむなんて疲れるだけよ
Feeling sad just wears me out
何も感じず過ごせばいいの
It's better to just live without feeling anything
戸惑う言葉与えられても
Even if I'm given words that confuse me...
自分の心　ただ上の空
My heart is just somewhere else
もし私から動くのならば　すべて変えるのなら黒にする
If I were to move on my own, if I were to change everything, I'd make it black
こんな自分に未来はあるの？
Is there a future for someone like me?
こんな世界に私はいるの？
Do I exist in a world like this?
今切ないの？今悲しいの？
Am I in pain now? Am I sad now?
自分のこともわからないまま
Without even knowing myself...
歩むことさえ疲れるだけよ
Even just walking is exhausting
人のことなど知りもしないわ
I don't know anything about others
こんな私も変われるのなら　もし変われるのなら白になる
If even I could change, if I could change, I'd become white
流れてく時の中ででも　気だるさが
Even in the midst of flowing time, listlessness...
ほらグルグル回って　私から離れる
See, it spins around and moves away from me
心も見えないわ　そう知らない
I can't even see my heart, I don't know it
自分から動くこともなく
Without moving of my own accord...
時の隙間に流され続けて知らないわ
Being washed away continuously into the gaps of time, I don't know...
周りのことなど　私は私それだけ
anything about my surroundings, I am me and that's all
夢見てる？なにも見てない？
Am I dreaming? Am I seeing nothing?
語るも無駄な自分の言葉
It's useless to speak my own words
避けよう 何も感じず 過ごせばいいの
Should I avoid it? It'd be fine to pass the time feeling nothing
戸惑う言葉 与えられても 自分の心 ただ上の空
Even if I'm given confusing words, my heart is just absent-minded
もし私から 動くのならば 全て変えるのなら 黒にする
If I were to make a move, if I were to change everything, I'd turn it black
動くのならば 全て壊すわ 全て壊すわ
If I make a move, I'll destroy everything, I'll destroy it all
悲しむならば 私の心 白く変われる？
If I were to grieve, could my heart turn white?
あなたのことも 私のことも 全てのことも まだ知らないの
About you, about me, about everything, I still don't know
重い瞼を 開けたのならば 全て壊すのなら 黒になれ
If I were to open my heavy eyelids, if I were to destroy everything, let it turn black
（ヴォーカリゼーション）
(Vocalization)
いつか君が瞳に灯す愛の光が
The light of love you'll one day light in your eyes
時を超えて 滅び急ぐ世界の夢を
Transcending time, the dreams of a world rushing towards ruin
確かに一つ 壊すだろう
Will surely destroy one of them
躊躇いを飲み干して
Drink down your hesitation
君が望むものは何？
What is it that you desire?
こんな欲深い憧れの行方に 儚い明日はあるの？
In the destination of such greedy longings, is there a fleeting tomorrow?
子供の頃夢に見てた 古の魔法のように
Like the ancient magic I dreamed of as a child
闇さえ砕く力で 微笑む君に会いたい
With a power that can crush even darkness, I want to see you smiling
怯えるこの手の中には 倒られた花と勇気
In these trembling hands are fallen flowers and courage
想いだけが頼る全て 光を呼び覚ます願い
My feelings are all I rely on, a wish that awakens the light
（ヴォーカリゼーション）
(Vocalization)
いつか君も誰かのために 強い力を望むのだろう
One day, you too will desire great power for someone's sake
愛が胸を捕らえた夜に 未知の言葉が生まれてくる
On the night love seized your heart, unknown words were born
迷わずに行けるなら 心が砕けてもいいわ
If I can go without straying, it's fine if my heart shatters
いつも目の前の悲しみに 立ち向かうための呪文が欲しい
I want a spell to confront the sorrow always before my eyes
君はまだ夢見る記憶 私は眠らない明日
You are still memories within a dream, I am a tomorrow that never sleeps
二人が出会う奇跡を 勝ち取るために進むの
Moving forward to grasp the miracle of our encounter
怯えるこの手の中には 倒られた花と刃
In these trembling hands are fallen flowers and a blade
想いだけが生きる全て 心に振りかざす願い
My feelings are all that live, a wish brandished in my heart
（ヴォーカリゼーション）
(Vocalization)
囚われた太陽の輝く
The radiance of the captured sun
不思議の国の本が好きだった頃
Back when I loved Alice in Wonderland books
願いはきっと叶うと教えるおとぎ話を信じた
I believed in fairy tales that taught that wishes always come true
光と影の中に
Within the light and the shadows
静かに咲き乱れていた
Quietly blooming in profusion
いにしえの魔法を優しく
The ancient magic gently
世界を変える力が
The power to change the world
その手にあると囁く
Whispers that it's in those hands
終わらない夢を見よう
Let's dream a dream that never ends
君と行く時の中で
Within the time I spend with you
想いだけが生きる全て
Feelings alone are all that lives
命を作るのは願い
What creates life is a wish
わー！
Whoa—!
アキちゃん、お誕生日おめでとう！
Aki-chan, happy birthday!
ありがとう！イェーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
いやー、今日は来てくれてありがとうございます。
Man, thank you so much for coming today.
いやいや、こちらこそですよ。呼んでくれてありがとうございます。
No, no, the pleasure is ours. Thank you for inviting us.
実はね、二人を呼んだのちょっと理由があって。 お、なんだなんだ？
Actually, there's a reason I invited you two. Oh, what is it?
前にアキロゼの4周年の時に、3人でKalafinaさんの曲、出させてもらったんだけど。
Previously, on AkiRose's 4th anniversary, the three of us released a cover of a Kalafina song.
やりましたねー。めっちゃ良かったやつね。そう、ハーモニーがね。
We did. That was a really great one. Yeah, the harmony...
もうね、ミオちゃんの歌も大好きだし、AZKiの歌も大好きだし、もう忘れられないの。
I love Mio-chan's singing and AZKi's singing so much, I just can't forget it.
分かる、分かる。
I get it, I get it.
だから、もう一回、このライブステージで3人で歌いたくて、今日は来てもらいました。
So, I wanted to sing as a trio on this live stage once again, and that's why I had you come today.
嬉しい！ありがとありがと。
So happy! Thank you, thank you.
だからこれからね、これを機にもっと何か3人で歌ったりとか、挑戦できたらめっちゃ嬉しい。
So, from now on, taking this opportunity, I'd be so happy if we could sing more as a trio or try new things.
いいんですか！？ハーモニーを重ねていきましょうよ。え、いいの！？
Is that okay!? Let's keep layering our harmonies. Wait, is it okay!?
嬉しい！やったー！
I'm so happy! Yay!
ユニット名とか欲しいな。確かに！欲しい！
I want a unit name or something. True! I want one!
なんかちょっと、世界目指せるぐらいの。
Something like, aiming for the world.
世界！世界の！世界のコンサートしようよ。
The world! Of the world! Let's do a world concert.
しようよ！
Let's!
世界に轟く、我らをね、したいということで。
We want to make ourselves known to the world.
この3人でライブとか、アコースティックとか、オーケストラライブとか！
Lives with this trio, acoustic shows, orchestra lives too!
うわー！え、良くないですか？そんなことをしてみたい。
Whoa—! Doesn't that sound great? I want to try that.
我らならできるかもしれない！できるできる！お願いします。
We might be able to do it! We can, we can! Please.
あれ？え、これは一体何ですか？
Huh? Wait, what on earth is this?
もしかして、このライブでみんなからの、なんかいいパワーで。
Maybe, with all the energy from everyone at this live.
なんかいいパワー来てる。ビジュアルじゃん、それ。なんだよ、そのパワー。
Some good power is coming. That's a visual! What is that power?
こちらがなんと、完成しました！なんだそれ！
This has finally been completed! What's that!
モノポリ
Monopoly
実は、この後、アキロゼの新曲が出ます！
Actually, a new AkiRose song will be out after this!
やったー！きたー！
Yay! It's here!
今回のライブの、壮大なテーマが詰まったような楽曲になっています。
It's a song that's packed with the grand theme of this live show.
ライブ終わりの日付が変わる時にリリースしますので、ぜひ買って聴いてください。
It'll be released at midnight after the live, so please buy it and have a listen.
みんな聴くぞー！
Everyone's gonna listen!
ではではでは、次の曲に行きますか。次の曲？え、新曲お披露目！？
Well then, shall we move on to the next song? Next song? Wait, a new song reveal!?
しちゃいます！え、今からってこと！？
I'm gonna do it! Wait, you mean right now!?
今から頑張ります！最後まで見逃せないですね。楽しみだー！
I'll do my best starting now! You can't miss it until the end. I'm excited!
お願いします。アキちゃん頑張ってね！ありがとー！またねー！
Please. Good luck, Aki-chan! Thank you! See you later!
モノポリー
作詞・作曲・編曲：なるみや
Monopoly
Lyrics, Composition, Arrangement: Narumiya
魅惑の言葉の裏面に忍ばせた
Concealed on the back of alluring words
1mgのスパイス
1mg of spice
たちまち華麗な指先で彩る
Instantly adorned by magnificent fingertips
本日のダイス
Today's dice
当たり前だって恐縮してちゃ
If you're too humble, thinking it's only natural,
生き残れないでしょう
you won't be able to survive, right?
率直に言って全てが欲しい
To be frank, I want it all
一人勝ちオールイン
A winner-take-all All-In
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない 際限なんてないじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens, there are no limits, right?
翻して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Overturning, being toyed with, shivers down the spine
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ 最低だって化けるでしょ
It's what you wanted even if you take a hit, right? Even at your worst, you'll transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に 終わりはない
Seeing through, being seen through, and therefore, there is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
Everything that throbs is non-fiction
嗜むはずでも たまには飲み過ぎて
Even if I'm just savoring it, I sometimes drink too much
1回休み
Lose one turn
周りもざわつく 思わぬうたた寝で
The surroundings get noisy because of an unexpected nap
2回休み
Lose two turns
切れる頭と勘だけじゃ
With just a sharp mind and intuition,
手に入らないもの
there are things you can't obtain
そこで射て見返せるならいい
If I can strike there and show them, it's fine
命懸けで楽しむわ
I'll enjoy it with my life on the line
天と地は意外と近くない
Heaven and earth aren't that close together
この通り命懸け
Just as I said, my life's on the line
たかがモノポリー されどお遊戯
It's only Monopoly, yet it's still a game
決める 想いで 故に 私は強い
I'll decide with my feelings, and therefore, I am strong
どうなっちゃってもいいじゃない 際限なんてないじゃない
It doesn't matter what happens, there are no limits, right?
翻して 翻弄されて ゾクゾク
Overturning, being toyed with, shivers down the spine
喰らっちゃっても本望でしょ 最低だって化けるでしょ
It's what you wanted even if you take a hit, right? Even at your worst, you'll transform, right?
見透かして 見透かされて 故に 終わりはない
Seeing through, being seen through, and therefore, there is no end
高鳴るこの全てノンフィクション
Everything that throbs is non-fiction
墜ちても昇ってもノンフィクション
Falling or rising, it's all non-fiction
葛飾ラプソディー
作詞：森雪之丞 作曲：堂島孝平
Katsushika Rhapsody
Lyrics: Yukinojo Mori, Composition: Kohei Dojima
中川に浮かぶ
Towards the sunset
夕陽をめがけて
floating on the Naka River
小石を蹴ったら
When I kicked a pebble,
靴まで飛んで
even my shoe flew off
ジョギングしていた
And I was laughed at
大工の頭に
by a jogging master carpenter
ガキのままだと
for still
笑われたのさ
being like a kid
どこかに元気を
Even if I've dropped
落っことしても
my energy somewhere
葛飾亀有
Katsushika Kameari
あくびを一つ
With a single yawn,
変わらない街並みが妙に優しいよ
the unchanging townscape is strangely kind
中央広場で
Leading a child's hand
子供の手を引く
in the central square,
太ったあの娘は
that girl who's gotten plump
初恋の人
is my first love
ゴンパチいけて
Gonpachi went off,
私らぶれた
and I was rejected
今も持てると
I was teased that
からかわれたよ
I could still be popular
何もいいこと
Even though nothing
なかったけれど
good happened
葛飾水元
Katsushika Mizumoto
流れる雲と ラプソディー口ずさみ
Humming a rhapsody with the floating clouds,
少し歩こうか
shall we walk a bit?
カラスがなくから
Since the crows are calling,
もう陽が暮れるね
the sun is already setting
焼き鳥ほおばり
Let's stuff our faces with yakitori
ビール飲もか
and drink some beer
とんがり帽子の
From the intake tower
取水塔から
with the pointed cap,
大気圏へと
into the atmosphere
夕陽が落ちる
the sunset falls
明日もこうして終わるんだね
Tomorrow will end like this too, won't it?
隠しかしたまま　幸せだって
Hiding things away, even if it's called happiness...
隠して気が付いた　馬鹿な本音だから
Because it's a foolish truth I realized by hiding it
どこかに元気をお落としても
Even if I lose my energy somewhere
隠しかめあり　あくびを一つ
Hiding things away, letting out a yawn
変わらない街並みが　妙に優しいや
The unchanging cityscape is strangely kind
アキロゼ生誕祭2026をご覧の皆様、いかがでしたでしょうか？
To everyone watching AkiRose Birthday 2026, how did you like it?
さて、ここからは大事なお知らせがあるので、最後までしっかり聞いていってね。
Now, there are some important announcements starting from here, so please listen carefully until the end.
まずはお知らせ1つ目。
First, the first announcement.
アキ・ローゼンタール2026誕生日グッズ、発売です！
Aki Rosenthal 2026 Birthday Goods are now on sale!
今回はライブの世界観をぎゅっと楽しんでもらえるグッズを頑張って制作いたしました。
This time, I worked hard to create goods that allow you to fully enjoy the world of the live performance.
なので今回のライブが良かったなーって思った方は、是非応援で購入していただくのもすごく嬉しいです！
So if you thought this live was great, I'd be very happy if you'd consider purchasing them to show your support!
それではまず1つ目のグッズ。
So, here's the first item.
Life is GAME ラバーマット！
Life is GAME Rubber Mat!
今回のイラストはLAM先生に描き下ろしていただきました。素敵なイラストありがとうございます！
The illustration for this one was newly drawn by LAM-sensei. Thank you for the wonderful illustration!
今回のライブの世界観をイメージしたイラストになっています。
The illustration is based on the world of this live performance.
めちゃくちゃセクシーで色っぽいけどかっこいいようなアキロゼになっています。
It's an AkiRose that's very sexy and sensual, yet cool at the same time.
ラバーマットで思う存分楽しんでください。
Please enjoy it to your heart's content with this rubber mat.
ちなみにサイズはカードゲームにぴったり。
By the way, the size is perfect for card games.
この意味分かるよね？
You know what that means, right?
2つ目のグッズが、
The second item is...
運命の5枚 タロット風アクリルスタンドセット！
The 5 Cards of Fate: Tarot-style Acrylic Stand Set!
アキロゼがあなたのことを占って背中を押してあげます。
AkiRose will tell your fortune and give you a push of encouragement.
1日の始まりや、何か運命を託したい、みたいなそんな時に使って楽しむ。
Enjoy using it at the start of your day, or when you want to entrust something to fate.
そして5枚バーンって飾っておけるので、見ても楽しめるようになっています。
And since you can display all five cards together, it's also enjoyable to look at.
占い方法は、この後紹介するアキロゼのASMRボイスと連動しております。
The fortune-telling method is linked with AkiRose's ASMR voice, which I'll introduce later.
飾っても楽しい、使っても楽しい、そのような連動グッズになっているので、是非ゲットしてください。
It's a linked item that's fun to display and fun to use, so please get yours.
続いてのグッズは、
The next item is...
アキロゼのトランプ！
AkiRose's Playing Cards!
作っちゃいました！
I went and made them!
こちら実際に遊んでいただけるトランプなので、たくさん予備も買ったほうがいいんじゃないかなと思います。
Since these are real playing cards you can actually play with, I think you might want to buy plenty of spares.
是非トランプでもアキロゼをたくさん楽しんでアピールもしてくださいね。
Please enjoy AkiRose through these cards and show them off as well.
続いてはこちら、アキロゼのカードケース！
Next is this: AkiRose's Card Case!
これはもちろん、トランプなど小物入れても大丈夫です。
Of course, you can use this for playing cards or other small items.
是非お家や持ち歩きに使ってね。
Please use it at home or when you're out and about.
そしてボイスの紹介です。
And now, the voice introduction.
今回もASMRボイスを特別に発売！
I'm releasing a special ASMR voice this time too!
アキとロゼがそれぞれ左右からあなたのことを誘惑しちゃうかも。
Aki and Rose might seduce you from the left and right respectively.
台本も頑張って書いたので是非是非たっぷり楽しんでもらえたら嬉しいです。
I worked hard on the script, so I'd be very happy if you enjoyed it to the fullest.
こちらボイスは「Life is GAME　アキとロゼの晩餐」
This voice is "Life is GAME: The Banquet of Aki and Rose"
こちらをメインとし、ASMRショートボイスとして先程の「運命の5枚　タロット風アクリルカード」と連動したショートボイスが入っております。
With that as the main content, it also includes ASMR short voices that are linked to the "5 Cards of Fate: Tarot-style Acrylic Cards" mentioned earlier.
ショートボイスのシャッフル・ランダム再生をして選ばれたボイスが、あなたの運命の1枚になります。
The voice selected by shuffling or random playback will be your single card of fate.
是非いろいろ楽しんでね。
Please enjoy it in various ways.
これらのグッズすべてが詰まったフルセット購入には、なんと特典も付いております。
The full set purchase, which includes all these items, even comes with a bonus!
今回のキービジュアルのイラストを使ったチケット風カードになっております。
It's a ticket-style card using this time's key visual illustration.
あなたはこのゲームに参加する？
Will you participate in this game?
こちらもライブの世界観を高めるアイテムになっているので是非ゲットしてください。
This is also an item that enhances the live experience, so please get it.
そして数量限定あります！
And, there's a limited quantity version!
直筆サインと箔押し複製メッセージが入ったものになっております。頑張って書きます。
This version includes a handwritten signature and a foil-stamped printed message. I'll work hard writing them.
そして数量限定が終わり次第、箔押しでの複製サインとメッセージが入ったチケット風カードになります。是非フルセット購入特典ゲットしてね。
Once the limited quantity version is gone, it will be a ticket-style card with a foil-stamped printed signature and message. Please get the full set purchase bonus.
大事な発売時間は、この後21時30分。
The important release time is after this, at 21:30.
21時30分にショップオープンです。是非登録など準備して備えておいてね。
The shop opens at 21:30. Please get ready by registering and so on.
続きましてお知らせ2つ目。
Moving on to the second announcement.
この後21時45分からメンバー限定のアフターライブを行います！
Starting at 21:45 tonight, I'll be holding a member-only after-live!
ライブ本編とはまた違う楽曲を披露する予定なので、是非お楽しみに。
I'm planning to perform songs different from the main concert, so please look forward to it.
今日メンバーになった方も是非是非見てね。
To those who became members today, please be sure to watch it too.
ちなみに過去のライブのメンバー限定アフターライブも見れちゃうと思うので、是非その...
By the way, I think you can also watch the member-only after-lives from past concerts, so please check those out...
辺りも見てみてね！
Take a look around too!
ちなみに、今回のサムネイルイラストは、
By the way, the thumbnail illustration for this time
メンバー限定で壁紙としてプレゼント予定です！お楽しみに。
will be a wallpaper gift for members! Look forward to it.
そして、お知らせ３つ目！
And the third announcement!
本日の生誕祭ライブの後も、お楽しみはまだまだ続きます。
After today's birthday live, the fun still continues.
なんと、ホロアースにて特別企画、
Actually, a special project in Holoearth,
アキ・ローゼンタール生誕祭アンコール in ホロアースを開催します！
Aki Rosenthal Birthday Encore in Holoearth will be held!
今回初披露した新曲『モノポリー』をホロアースで歌っちゃいます！
I'll sing the new song 'Monopoly' in Holoearth!
いろんな角度からアキロゼのパフォーマンスや演出をじっくりと見てみてくださいね。
Please watch the performance and production from various angles.
さらに、ホロアースだけのMCパートもたっぷりあるので、ぜひぜひ会いに来てください！
There's an exclusive MC part, so please come see me!
開催日は、３月13日、３月13日です。
The date is March 13th, March 13th.
詳細は、ホロアース公式Xをチェックしてね！
Check the official Holoearth X for details!
そして、最後のお知らせが、新曲『モノポリー』！
And the final announcement is the new song, 'Monopoly'!
本日日付が変わる頃にリリースされますので、各音楽配信サービスからぜひ購入してね！
It'll be released at midnight! Please buy it from streaming services!
たくさん聴いてね！
Please listen to it a lot!
振付も歌もとってもキャッチーなので、
The choreography and song are very catchy,
覚えてみんなで楽しんでもらえる、愛されるような楽曲になってくれたら嬉しいなって思っています。
so I hope it becomes a beloved track that everyone enjoys.
また後日ライブ配信で新曲『モノポリー』だったり、
I want to do a stream later about 'Monopoly'
今回のライブに触れた後日談など語ったり、一緒に見たりなどしたいなと思っているので、
and share stories about this live while watching it together,
ぜひチャンネル登録、高評価ぽちっ、
so please subscribe, hit the like button,
通知もオンにしてるという人は今ぽちっとしてね！絶対絶対また会いに来てね！
and turn on notifications! Please come see me again!
それでは。
And now...
運命は時に残酷、
Fate is sometimes cruel,
あなたが選びたくて選んだものではないかもしれない。
it might not be something you wanted to choose.
だけど、いつでもあなたの人生はあなたのもの。
But your life is always yours.
人生は一度きり、
Life is a one-time thing,
やり直しのきかないこのゲーム。
a game you can't redo.
あなたは、どう楽しむ？
How will you enjoy it?
【主催者】 アキ・ローゼンタール
[Organizer] Aki Rosenthal
【出演者】 赤見かるび 天鬼ぷるる ズズ 律可 癒月ちょこ 森カリオペ 鷹嶺ルイ IRyS 水宮枢 AZKi 大神ミオ
[Cast] Akami Karubi, Amaki Pururu, Zuz, Rikka, Yuzuki Choco, Mori Calliope, Takane Lui, IRyS, Mizumiya Sui, AZKi, Ookami Mio
【歌唱ゲスト】 かしわねこ dtto. げっつん アルランディス おおはらMEN だいだら marunnn Axel Syrios 甘狼このみ 群青ロマン 那和ツムグ 梟雄しろや かんせる たちばな 狂蘭メロコ 水瀬 わき ろぜっくびん しろまんた 歌衣メイカ 花ノ木まる おなつのにびたし Middleeetv ゆう。 シード 荒咬オウガ ドンピシャ ひぐち/ひぐち! 如月れん 玉餅かずよ ロボ子さん まぎー3 ととみっくす 渋谷ハル 日ノ隈らん 猫次つな 秋雪こはく 白雪レイド
[Vocal Guests] Kashiwa Neko, dtto., Gettsun, Arurandeisu, Ohara MEN, Daidara, marunnn, Axel Syrios, Amagami Konomi, Gunjou Roman, Nawa Tsugumu, Torii Shiroya, Kanseru, Tachibana, Kyouran Meroko, Mizuse, Waki, Rozekubin, Shiromanta, Ui Meika, Hanonoki Maru, Onatsu no Nipitashi, Middleeetv, Yuu., Seed, Araki Ouga, Donpisha, Higuchi/Higuchi!, Kisaragi Ren, Tamamochi Kazuyo, Roboco-san, Magi-3, Totomix, Shibuya Hal, Hinokuma Ran, Nekotsugi Tsuna, Akisetsu Kohaku, Shirayuki Raid
【振付制作】 ミユクニニジマ 【バックダンサー】 高橋千里 RISAKO Mishio Tokita Shiopen
[Choreography] Miyuki Nijima [Back Dancers] Takahashi Chisato, RISAKO, Mishio Tokita, Shiopen
【サムネイルイラスト】 澄夜 咲星 【ロゴ制作】 柊椋
[Thumbnail Art] Sumiya Akiboshi [Logo Production] Hiiragi
【モノポリー ジャケットイラスト】 しまぐち ニケ 【モノポリー ジャケットロゴ】 ミナトデザイン
[Monopoly Jacket Illustration] Shimaguchi Nike [Monopoly Jacket Logo] Minato Design
【音源制作】 トライフロンティア合同会社 クックルP 夜湾/yowan. Sumia 夢魅たび ジョウコウ 宮内椋太 山本こーすけ 合同会社VESSEL LIFE sa-sara SAZA 株式会社音響ハウス 大島健志 内柴海 山内翔平 呂秉動
[Audio Production] Trifrontier LLC, Kukkuru P, Yowan/yowan., Sumia, Yumetabi, Joukou, Miyauchi Ryota, Yamamoto Kosuke, VESSEL LIFE: sa-sara, SAZA, Sound House: Oshima Kenji, Uchishiba Umi, Yamauchi Shohei, Ro Gidou
【背景 / OL映像制作】 ぺたぺた（スタジオメイイビー） U（スタジオメイイビー） 茶人百（スタジオメイイビー） Quma (Maybe-Delta) H!B!K! (Maybe-Delta) ななせむぎ りずにか Nザミー 堕地るん ゆーせき YuUma ぼぞぐ
[Background / Video Production] Petapeta (Studio Maybe), U (Studio Maybe), Chajinhyaku (Studio Maybe), Quma (Maybe-Delta), H!B!K! (Maybe-Delta), Nanasemugi, Rizunika, N Zamii, Ojirun, Yu-seki, YuUma, Bozo-gu
【OP制作】 ぺたぺた（スタジオメイイビー） 茶人百（スタジオメイイビー） 野村生淡（スタジオメイイビー） ぼぞぐ
[OP Production] Petapeta (Studio Maybe), Chajinhyaku (Studio Maybe), Nomura Namadan (Studio Maybe), Bozo-gu
【Special Thanks】 ロゼ隊 ALL STAFF and You
[Special Thanks] Rose-tai, ALL STAFF and You
Member Only After Live
2/17 21:45 Start
Starting February 17, 21:45
START / END
END